– Ali, my darling!
- Mein lieber Ali!
What’s the matter, didn’t you miss me at all?
Was ist los, hast du mich garnicht vermisst?
– And did you miss me? Did you even think about if I have something to eat and drink?
- Hast du mich denn vermisst? Hast du dich denn gefragt ob ich zu essen und zu trinken habe?
– Don’t talk nonsense.
- Red keinen Unsinn.
Don’t get in a huff.
Spiel nicht den Beleidigten.
Have you ever come to visit me even once?
Hast du mich jemals auch nur einmal besucht?
– I’m afraid of police and prisons. – Isn’t my mother here?
- Ich hab Angst vor Polizisten und Gefängnissen. - Ist Mutter nicht da?
– Haven’t you heard? When she left the hospital she went completely nuts.
- Nicht gehört? Nach dem Spitalaufenthalt ist sie erst recht übergeschnappt.
We had to admit her to a mental hospital. – Serves her right.
Wir mussten sie in die Irrenanstalt einweisen. - Geschieht ihr recht.
She’ll come to her senses.
Das wird ihr helfen zur Besinnung zu kommen.
– I think her condition is not... – Okay, okay! We’ll take care of it tomorrow.
- Ich denke es geht ihr garnicht gut... - Okay, okay! Wir kümmern uns morgen darum.
– First let’s satisfy our desires, no?
- Lass uns zuerst die Sehnsucht stillen, ha?
– Uhm no, there’s no food at home... – Okay!
- Ach nein, es gibt kaum was zu essen... - Verstanden!
– I’ll arrange something. – Okay.
- Ich werde etwas arrangieren. - Okay.
So you didn’t miss me at all, huh?
Du hast mich also garnicht vermisst, ha?
In that case neither did I miss you!
Wenn das so ist, dann habe ich dich auch nicht vermisst!